Reading Protecting Pandas Simon is reading an article by a panda-keeper.
Here is the article.
She Wong in safe hands.
Tiny, pink and quiet with eyes closed.
She Wong was just one hundred grams when I first saw her.
Her birth brought much happiness to us.
We named her She Wong because it means hope.
In the beginning, She Wong couldn't see, hear or even move.
We gave her round-the-clock care.
At six months old, she began to eat bamboo.
Half a year later, she weighed over 35 kilograms.
There is nothing more satisfying than seeing She Wong grow into a big ball of fur.
When she was 20 months old, she learnt to look after herself.
She Wong has a happy life here.
However, giant pandas in the wild face serious problems.
They are very special animals.
It is difficult for them to have babies.
Even if baby pandas are born, they may easily get sick and die.
Also, they live mainly on bamboo, but the bamboo forests are becoming smaller and smaller.
As a result, pandas may not have a place to live or enough food to eat.
Luckily, the government has taken action.
There are laws to protect giant pandas and more nature reserves for them to live in.
What's more, scientists are working hard to help pandas have more babies.
Thanks to all the efforts, the number of giant pandas is increasing.
But they still need our protection.
We believe things will get better and better.
For where there is She Wong, there is hope.